RG 005:038, Office of the Governor: Lowell P. Weicker, Jr. (1991-1995)
Connecticut State Library
- Series 1. Constituent Correspondence, 1987-1994; 1995-040
  - Agency Files (Box 3)
    - Policy and Management, Office of, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 1-9)
    - Policy and Management, Office of, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 10-13)
    - Policy and Management, Office of, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Public Health and Addiction Services, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 15-24)
    - Public Health, Dept. of, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 25-31)
    - Public Safety, Dept. of, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 1-13)
    - Public Safety, Dept. of, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 14-22)
    - Public Safety, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 23-30)
    - Public Safety, Dept. of, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 1-4)
    - Public Utility Control, Dept. of, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 5-6)
    - Public Utility Control, Dept. of, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 7-12)
    - Public Utility Control, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 13-16)
    - Public Utility Control, Dept. of, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Public Works, Dept. of, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 18-19)
    - Public Works, Dept. of, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 20-22)
    - Public Works, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 23-25)
    - Public Works, Dept. of, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Real Estate Commission, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Real Estate Commission, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Real Estate Commission, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - Rehabilitation Services, Division of, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Rehabilitation Services, Bureau of, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - Rehabilitation Services, Bureau of, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - Rehabilitation Services, Bureau of, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - Retirement Commission, State Employee, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - Retirement Commission, State Employee, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - Revenue Services, Dept. of, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 1-20)
    - Revenue Services, Dept. of, A-F, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 21-28)
    - Revenue Services, Dept. of, G-Z, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 1-12)
    - Revenue Services, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 13-23)
    - Revenue Services, Dept. of, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 24-28)
    - Secretary of the State, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Secretary of the State, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 2-4)
    - Secretary of the State, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Secretary of the State, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Social Services, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 7-14)
    - Social Services, Dept. of, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Special Revenue, Division of, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 16-17)
    - Special Revenue, Division of, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 18-22)
    - Special Revenue, Division of, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 23-25)
    - Special Revenue, Division of, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 26-27)
    - Teachers' Retirement Board, 1991, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Transportation, Dept. of, A-B, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 29-33)
    - Transportation, Dept. of, C-S, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 1-23)
    - Transportation, Dept. of, T-Z, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 1-3)
    - Transportation, Dept. of, A-L, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 4-25)
    - Transportation, Dept. of, M-Z, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 1-19)
    - Transportation, Dept. of, A-F, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 20-30)
    - Transportation, Dept. of, G-Z, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 1-28)
    - Transportation, Dept. of, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 29-38)
    - Treasurer, Office of the State, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Treasurer, Office of the State, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Treasurer, Office of the State, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Treasurer, Office of the State, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - U.S. Senators, Christopher Dodd, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - U.S. Senators, Christopher Dodd, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - U.S. Senators, Joseph Lieberman, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - U.S. Senators, Joseph Lieberman, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - University of Connecticut, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 9-10)
    - University of Connecticut, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - $690 million G.O. financing rated AA by Fitch press release, 1991 September 12 (Box 39)
    - Veterans' Affairs, Dept. of, 1991 (Box 39 13)
    - Veterans' Affairs, Dept. of, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Veterans' Affairs, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Veterans' Affairs, Dept. of, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Victim Services, Commission on, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Victim Services, Commission on, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Victim Services, Commission on, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Women, Permanent Commission on the Status of, 1992-1994 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Worker's Compensation Commission, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 21-25)
    - Worker's Compensation Commission, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 26-31)
    - Worker's Compensation Commission, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 32-36)
    - Worker's Compensation Commission, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 37-38)
  - Greeting, Support, and Thank You Letters (Box 40)
    - Greeting letters, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 1-7)
    - Reelection, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 8-10)
    - Reelection decision, 1993 September-October (Box 40, Folder 11-12)
    - Support letters, 1991-1992 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Support letters, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 14-19)
    - Thank you from Gov. Weicker, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 20-25)
    - Thank you to Gov. Weicker, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 26-27)
  - Issue Letters (Box 41)
    - A Connecticut Party, 1991-1992 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Abortion, 1991-1993 (Box 41, Folder 2-3)
    - Acid rain, 1993 February (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Aging, Dept. of, Budget cuts, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Aging, Dept. of, Reorganization, 1993 January (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - AIDS, 1992 June (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Amtrak electrification project, 1993 October-December (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Annexation of land by the Mashantucket Pequots, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 9-11)
    - Appointments, 1991-1992 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Autographed photos, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Autographed photos, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Autographed photos, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Blue Hills Hospital residential program, 1993 February (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Bottle Bill II, 1993 January-July (Box 41, Folder 17-25)
    - Bridgeport incarceration facility, 1993 June-July (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Bridgeport office, 1993 April (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Budget, A-G, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 28-34)
    - Budget, H-Z, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 1-10)
    - Budget, Citizen advocacy, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Budget, Petitions, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Budget, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 13-21)
    - Budget, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 22-27)
    - Budget, News clippings, 1992-1993 (Box 42, Folder 28)
    - Budget, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 29)
    - Busing to private schools, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 1-2)
    - Cablevision of Connecticut, 1993 March-April (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Casino gambling, 1991-1993 (Box 43, Folder 4-13)
    - Casino gambling, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Cheshire corrections facility, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Child desegregation, 1992-1993 March (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Cigarette sales by the Golden Hill Paugussetts, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - ConnPace, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 18-19)
    - Cooperative Library Service Units budget cuts, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Cooperative Library Service Units budget cuts, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 21-30)
    - Cooperative Library Service Units budget cuts, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 31)
    - County dispatch services, 1993 February (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - David Brinkley show, 1992 February (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Death penalty, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 3-5)
    - Death penalty, 1994 June (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Drug free America, 1993 April (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Eagle scouts, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 8-13)
    - Eagle scouts, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 14-20)
    - Eagle scouts, 1994 January-May (Box 44, Folder 21-23)
    - Education budget cuts, 1992 October-1993 June (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - Electric transmission line between Bridgeport and Norwalk, 1993 June-1994 March (Box 44, Folder 25-26)
    - Electric transmission line, New Canaan, 1993 February-November (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - Emissions contract, 1993 December-1994 January (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - Farmington River wild and scenic river designation, 1992 May-1993 May (Box 44, Folder 29-32)
    - Federal issues, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 33-39)
    - Federal issues, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 1-5)
    - Federal issues, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 6-13)
    - Federal issues, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 14-15)
    - Federal Unemployment Act, 1992 January-September (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Former inmate pardons, 1993 February-March (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Gambling, 1992-1993 (Box 45, Folder 18-20)
    - Gold Scout gold award, 1994 February-April (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Golden Hill Paugussett Indians, 1994 January (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - Grants, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - Gun control, 1993 December-1994 June (Box 45, Folder 24-26)
    - Guns for Goods program, 1994 April-June (Box 45, Folder 27)
    - Gynecologists as primary care physicians, 1994 January (Box 45, Folder 28)
    - Hartford Civic Center / hockey team, 1993 April-May (Box 45, Folder 29)
    - Hispanic affairs, 1991-1994 (Box 45, Folder 30)
    - History and Genealogy (State Library), 1994 January (Box 45, Folder 31)
    - Homeless, 1991-1993 (Box 45, Folder 32)
    - Income tax news clippings, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 33)
    - Income tax repair bill, 1991-1993 (Box 45, Folder 34-35)
    - Inmate pardons, 1993 December-1994 January (Box 45, Folder 36)
    - J.T. Slocumb Company layoffs, 1993 February (Box 45, Folder 37)
    - Land claim by the Golden Hill Paugussett Indians, 1993 April-December (Box 46, Folder 1-3)
    - Lapointe, Richard, 1993 February-March (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Legal issues, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 6-11)
    - Legal issues, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 12-14)
    - Legal issues, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 15-16)
    - Legal issues, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 17-18)
    - Legislation, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 19-25)
    - Legislation, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 1-9)
    - Legislation, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 10-23)
    - Legislation, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 1-6)
    - Local issues, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 7-8)
    - Local issues, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 9-11)
    - Local issues, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 12-13)
    - Local issues, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Licensing and inspection fees, 1993 March (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Litchfield Correctional Center closing, 1993 April (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Medicare (S.B. 1055), 1993 June August (Box 48, Folder 17-20)
    - Mental Health, Dept. of, budget cuts, 1992-1993 (Box 48, Folder 21-24)
    - Mental health merger (S.B. 93), 1994 March (Box 48, Folder 25-26)
    - Mental Retardation, Dept. of, budget cuts, 1992 September-1993 February (Box 48, Folder 27)
    - Morgan Street Detention Center closing, 1993 June-September (Box 48, Folder 28)
    - Motor Vehicles, Dept. of, Bridgeport office relocation, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Multiple issues, 1992-1992 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - National Day of Prayer, 1993 January-May (Box 49, Folder 2-6)
    - National Governors' Association, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - No tax penalties, 1993 February-April (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - North Atlantic Free Trade Agreement, 1993 August-October (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Northeast Connecticut Alcohol Council, 1993 March (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Nursing home allowances, 1993 July-November (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Out of state requests, 1993 December-1994 February (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Parker, William, 1992-1993 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Patriots football in Hartford, 1993 July-September (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Plainfield Greyhound Park, 1993 February (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Political, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Political, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Political, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Political, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Pratt & Whitney Aircraft Co. layoffs, 1993 April (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - Purchase of service project (rebidding), 1994 February-May (Box 49, Folder 21-22)
    - Recipes, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 23-25)
    - Recipes, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 26-28)
    - Recipes, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 29)
    - Recipes, 1994 January-March (Box 49, Folder 30)
    - Recommendations, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 31)
    - Recreation and Natural Heritage Trust Program, 1992 December-1993 February (Box 49, Folder 32)
    - Recreation and Natural Heritage Trust Program, 1994 January-March (Box 49, Folder 33)
    - Resume responses, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 34)
    - Resume responses, 1994 January-February (Box 49, Folder 35)
    - Route 7 (Super 7), 1992 (Box 49, Folder 36-37)
    - Route 59 and Merritt Parkway, 1992 August (Box 49, Folder 38)
    - Same sex marriage, 1993 September (Box 49, Folder 39)
    - Seawolf submarine program, 1992 March (Box 49, Folder 40)
    - Separation of powers, 1993 April (Box 49, Folder 41)
    - Sexual orientation discrimination, 1992 July-1993 November (Box 49, Folder 42)
    - Shakespeare Theater, 1993 August-November (Box 49, Folder 43)
    - Southbury Training School, 1993 December-1994 February (Box 49, Folder 44)
    - Southern New England Telephone (SNET) rate increases, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 45)
    - Special elections on Saturday, 1992-1993 (Box 49, Folder 46)
    - Spranzo v. Taylor accident, 1994 March (Box 49, Folder 47)
    - State employee layoff news clippings, 1991-1992 (Box 49, Folder 48)
    - Statute of limitations for securities fraud (H.B. 7290), 1993 (Box 50, Folder 1-5)
    - Suggestions, 1993 February-March (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Summer internships, 1991 April-June (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Tax suggestions, 1993 December (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Taxes news clippings, 1991-1992 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Toddy Hill and Still Hill (Sandy Hook, Conn.) residents protest of power station, 1993 January (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Tourism, 1991 February-June (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Unemployment compensation, 1993 April (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - United Way, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - University of Connecticut branch closings, 1993 February-March (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - University of Connecticut budget cuts, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - University of Connecticut, School of Allied Health closing, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 16-20)
    - University of Connecticut, School of Family Studies closing, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 21-22)
    - Valley Transit budget cuts, 1993 March-April (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - Volunteers, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - Welfare reform, 1992 December (Box 50, Folder 25)
    - Worker's Compensation system, 1992 November-1993 May (Box 50, Folder 26-27)
    - Yale New Haven Hospital 1993 budget, 1992 September (Box 50, Folder 28)
    - Address lists and form letters, 1991-1994 (Box 50, Folder 29-36)
  - Mag Letters (Box 51)
    - Issue letters, 1991-1992 (Box 51, Folder 1-2)
    - Historical file, 1991-1993 (Box 51, Folder 3-7)
    - One time letters, 1991, undated (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Letters (Box 51)
    - 1991 (Box 51, Folder 9-23)
    - 1992 (Box 52, Folder 1-24)
    - 1993 (Box 53, Folder 1-15)
    - 1994 (Box 53, Folder 16-33)
  - Audiovisual and Published Material (Box 54)
- Series 2. Press Files, 1991-1994; 1995-031
  - Research America, What is it?, 1990 August 23 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Governor-elect Weicker makes key appointments, 1990 November 16 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Inaugural remarks by Gov. Weicker, 1991 January 9 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Analysis of Gov. Weicker's plan and the Finance Committee's alternative, 1991 March 14 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Gov. Weicker nominates nine to the Board of Parole, 1991 April 17 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Connecticut Housing Finance Authority (CHFA), 1991 April 23 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Ethics Commission nominations, 1991 April 23 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Overcrowding Commission appointments, 1991 April 23 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Tax information released, 1991 April 23 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Claims Commissioner nominated, 1991 April 29 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Dept. of Children and Youth Services Advisory Board, 1991 April 29 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Freedom of Information Commission renominations, 1991 April 29 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Gelston nominated to siting council, 1991 April 29 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Gengras nominated to head Convention Center Authority, 1991 April 29 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Kratovil nominated to Gaming Commission, 1991 April 29 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Merchant nominated as Consumer Counsel, 1991 April 29 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Nominations to Bradley International Commission, 1991 April 29 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Sherry Banks-Cohn named Arts Commission Chair, 1991 April 29 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - State Labor Board nominations, 1991 April 29 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Architectural Licensing Board and Real Estate Commission appointments, 1991 April 30 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Indian gaming, 1991 April 30 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Veto of traffic quotas, 1991 April 30 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Statement of Gov. Weicker on signing of H.B. 7133 for gay rights, 1991 May 1 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Superior Court judges, 1991 May 1 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Miller appointed as Connecticut Health and Educational Facilities Authority (CHEFA) member, 1991 May 6 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Ethics, 1991 May 7 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Connecticut receives assistance form National Governors" Association (NGA), 1991 May 10 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Energy conservation program on-line, 1991 May 10 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Two nominated to Board of Pardons, 1991 May 10 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Bipartisan letter on spending caps, 1991 May 14 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Connecticut wins state grant given by National Science Foundation, 1991 May 14 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Casino gambling, 1991 May 16 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Letter to Manuel Lujan on proposed gaming, 1991 May 17 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Connecticut Health and Educational Facilities Authority and Connecticut Higher Education Supplemental Loan Authority appointments, 1991 May 17 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Medical Examining Board, 1991 May 17 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - State Parks, 1991 May 17 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Letter to Sen. Gary A. Hale, 1991 May 23 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Ansonia Copper & Brass, 1991 May 24 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Base closure, 1991 May 28 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Copy of magazine article on "The States, A Special Report;" FW ranking of states, 1991 May 28 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - National Institutes of Health (NIH) dedicates building to Gov. Weicker, 1991 May 30 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station appointment, 1991 May 31 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Budget veto, 1991 May 31 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Veto of S.H.B. 6229, 1991 June 3 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Connecticut Housing Finance Authority (CHFA) mortgages, 1991 June 4 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Student Advisory Council, 1991 June 4 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Trooper death, 1991 June 5 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Veto of S.S.B. 623, 1991 June 6 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Milk pricing law, 1991 June 7 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Bridgeport bill, 1991 June 10 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Governor's Budget Summary Revised, 1991 June 11 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Veto H.B. 5539, 1991 June 11 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Appointments, 1991 June 14 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Camp Weicker, 1991 June 14 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Gov. Weicker's Youth Action Awards, 1991 June 17 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - 1991 Dairy Farm of Distinction Awards, 1991 June 18 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Appointments, 1991 June 19 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Community Colleges, 1991 June 19 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Small Business and Marketing Authority, 1991 June 19 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Gov. Weicker's appointments, 1991 June 25 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - A. Searle Field appointment, 1991 June 27 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - University of Connecticut Board of Trustees, 1991 June 27 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Bills signed, 1991 June 28 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Bills signed, 1991 June 28 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Tentative plan to deliver essential state services, 1991 June 28 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - S.H.B. 5203 on death penalty, 1991 June 28 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - The People's Budget, undated (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Veto of Emergency Certified Bill 8006, 1991 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Constitutional spending cap to limit state spending, undated (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Coalition II: Flaws, 1991 July 1 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Essential services plan outlined, 1991 July 1 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Gov. Weicker implements essential services plan, 1991 July 2 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Gov. Weicker continues essential services plan, 1991 July 2 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - State beaches to reopen, 1991 July 3 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Connecticut State University trustees, 1991 July 5 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Veto S.H.B. 6242, 1991 July 5 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Reopening of government, 1991 July 7 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Continuing resolution, 1991 July 9 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Gov. Weicker's statement to the people, 1991 July 16 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Connecticut Alcohol and Drug Abuse Commission (CADAC), 1991 July 19 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - A proposal to the General Assembly, undated (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Northeast Utilities nuclear incident reports, undated (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Various appointments, 1991 July 29 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Appointments, 1991 July 31 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Coalition III: Flaws, 1991 August 3 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Larson response to Weicker, comments on Coalition III, undated (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Coalition III executive orders, 1991 August 4 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Gov. Weicker issues executive order, permits continued government operations, 1991 August 5 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Coalition III veto message, 1991 August 7 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Gov. Weicker speech about veto of Coalition III budget, 1991 August 7 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Veto speech, 1991 August 7 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Grandma Smith, 1991 August 8 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Various appointments, 1991 August 9 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Piggyback proposal, 1991 August 15 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Where are the cuts, 1991 August 15 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Harbormaster press release, 1991 August 16 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - City of Bridgeport, public safety emergency letter, 1991 August 19 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Hurricane Bob, 1991 August 19 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - The Connecticut Comeback Plan, Senators Spellman, Hale, & Herbst, 1991 August 20 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Superior Court Judge nominated, Robert I. Berdon, 1991 August 26 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Disaster relief, 1991 August 26 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Long term care insurance, 1991 August 29 (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Alan Schoenhaus, 1991 August 29 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - President Bush declares Connecticut a disaster area from Hurricane Bob, 1991 August 30 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Government study group appointments, 1991 September 4 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Letter to Bridgeport Mayor Moran reiterating State's position on assistance to city, 1991 September 9 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Cibes letter to Federal Emergency Management Agency on additional assistance to counties, 1991 September 10 (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Gov. Weicker makes appointments, 1991 September 10 (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA) approval, 1991 September 11 (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - Connecticut's $690 million G.O. financing rated AA by Fitch press release, 1991 September 12 (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - Response to bond ratings, 1991 September 13 (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - Gov. Weicker makes appointments, 1991 September 17 (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - Gov. Weicker's speech on Connecticut Mental Health Center 25th anniversary, 1991 September 21 (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Appointments to Council of Agricultural Development, 1991 September 24 (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Dept. Of Housing small cities grant, 1991 September 25 (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - Drug Enforcement Program and federal Drug Control and System Improvement Program grant funds, 1991 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - National education goals summary, 1991 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - Where does the money go?, 1991 October 3 (Box 1, Folder 118)